<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Tse-Hsun (Peter) Chen&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Tse-Hsun (Peter) Chen&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Tse-Hsun (Peter) Chen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Queen&#39;s University in September 2016. I was a member of the Software Analysis and Intelligence Lab (SAIL) and I was supervised by an amazing supervisor Ahmed E. Hassan. Before that, I received my MSc from Queen&#39;s University (under the same supervisor), and BSc in Computer Science from the University of British Columbia. During my PhD, I worked as an embedded researcher in the Performance Engineering department at BlackBerry from January 2013 to December 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/news/</guid>
      <description>[Aug 2023] Congrats to Zhenhao, An Ran, and the co-authors on the acceptance of our ASE paper Are They All Good? Studying Practitioners&amp;rsquo; Expectations on the Readability of Log Messages! [July 2023] Congrats to my PhD student An Ran Chen! He will join the University of Alberta as a tenure-track assistant professor in the fall! [June 2023] I will serve as a PC on the Research Track of FSE and MSR!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description> SOEN 7481 (Fall 2018, 2019): Software Verification and Testing SOEN 691 (Winter 2018): Mining Large Software System Data for DevOps SOEN 341 (Winter 2018, 2019, 2020, Fall 2019): Software Process SOEN 342 (Fall 2017): Software Requirements and Specifications  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students</title>
      <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/students/</guid>
      <description>MSc Students
 Misheelt (Mia) Munkhjargal Nakhla Rafi Lorena Barreto Feng Lin  PhD Students
 Dong Jae Kim Arthur Vitui Wei Liu Zehao Wang Yi Wen Heng Zeyang Ma  Alumni
 An Ran Chen; 2023 (PhD); Tenure-Track Assistant Professor at the University of Alberta Shouvick Mondal, 2022 (Post-Doc); Tenure-Track Assistant Professor at IIT Gandhinagar Zhenhao Li, 2022 (PhD); Principal Research Engineer at Huawei Tarek Makkouk, 2023 (MSc) Steven Locke, 2021 (MSc); First Employment: Morgan Stanley Zehao Wang, 2021 (MSc); Continued as PhD student at SPEAR Zi Peng, 2020 (MSc); First Employment: Tangerine Software Zhenhao Li, 2019 (MSc); Continued as PhD student at SPEAR An Ran Chen, 2019 (MSc); Continued as PhD student at SPEAR Hugo Enrique Ochoa, 2019 (BSc) Jacqlyn Bender, 2019 (BSc)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/services/</guid>
      <description>Organizing Committee and Journal Editor
 Co-editor of the Special Issue on Software Engineering and DevOps, Journal of Information Science and Engineering (JISE), 2021. The 12th International Conference on Performance Engineering (ICPE), Co-Chair of the Artifact Evaluation Track, 2021. Co-editor of the Special Issue on Software Performance, Empirical Software Engineering Journal (EMSE), 2020. Co-editor of the Special Issue on Collective Knowledge in Software Engineering, Empirical Software Engineering Journal (EMSE), 2020. The 8th International Workshop on Load Testing and Benchmarking of Software Systems (LTB), Program Chair, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petertsehsun.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>